opportunity authority out in two is in the patient by pastor of first assembly of
Dodgers for the infrasal right in the thanks for being here tonight.
We're about to gather heavily in follow me thank you for your wonderful grace and
mercy upon us as we celebrate this resurrection season.
Thank you Lord for this wonderful weather for blessing our city.
We pray continue to bless our businesses, our city council that giving them wisdom and all
directions.
I'll be thank you for the families and those that serve in this community, our first
responders, Lord and those that let's our community of the safety that they give us.
May you just bless this community with your mother Grace as you just move great
mountains for us in Jesus' precious day.
Amen.
Please join me in the pledge.
I pledge allegiance to the God of the United States of America and this is a privilege
for which it stands.
One nation, under God, in the name of the Lord.
Thank you.
Okay.
Adam four is public input and unscheduled personal appearances.
And then when the honest was to address the authority on any of the agenda items.
There'd be none.
I don't fire as a consent agenda.
If there are no questions on you outside of the International Motion to Approve.
No.
Approve.
And a second please.
We'll call.
Aye.
Four starts.
All right.
I made this new business and any business, anyone?
Item nine.
Excuse me.
That was out of nine.
Item ten is staff reports.
Reports are in your packet.
Staff available for questions if you have any.
Item 11 is trustee community announcements in the announcements.
Item 12 is adjournment.
Do we have a motion to adjourn the SQA?
I'll make a motion.
And I'll second that roll call please.
Four starts.
Aye.